## **Christian Milicevic**

Email: <a href="mailto:cmilicevic3@gmail.com">cmilicevic3@gmail.com</a>

**Mobile**: Supplied on request

## **Summary**

Recent graduate of the Queensland University of Technology (QUT) commencing a career in software development/programming.

In November 2020, I completed a Bachelor of Games and Interactive Environments (Software Technologies) at QUT. I achieved an aggregate GPA at Distinction level. My degree combined games programming and computer science. I also have a Diploma in Game Design which I received in 2017. I have considerable experience in casual employment within the warehousing sector, the events industry and a mechanical environment. I enjoy team-based work, meeting with people from diverse backgrounds and experiences, and I thrive on challenges that involve multiple responsibilities. For more information about me and to view my portfolio of work, please visit the following website:

https://www.christianmilicevic.com/

#### Location

Western suburbs, Brisbane, Australia

### Citizenship

Australian

#### Driver's Licence

Queensland Open Licence (Car - manual)

### **Transport**

Own vehicle

#### **Hobbies/Interests**

Car enthusiast IT enthusiast Health & Fitness

## **Key Skills**

- Demonstrated ability to work as part of a team
- Demonstrated organisational skills and the ability to deal with multiple responsibilities at the same time, including problem solving
- Demonstrated ability to work effectively without supervision
- Demonstrated ability to work in a busy environment and to be selfmotivated during quieter times
- Flexible and accommodating approach to work
- Respectful and polite manner with a focus on providing customers with a friendly and efficient service
- Good at adjusting to new environments and meeting new challenges
- Good at establishing relationships and maintaining long-term contacts
- Excellent skills in IT (see opposite) and the ability to assist others to improve their use of technology
- IT-specific skills include:
  - Game programming mathematics (Vector, Matrices, Coordinates, Trigonometry)
  - Types of Algorithms and Algorithm Efficiency
  - AI (A\*, Greedy Search and NavMesh)
  - User feedback and testing
  - Source control
  - Debugging
  - Efficient and effective code comments

#### IT Skills

Proficient with the following industry-based programs:

- Visual Studios
- .NET
- .NET Win Forms
- C#
- HTML & CSS
- Python
- MySQL/SQL Server
- Github & Source Tree
- Bit Bucket
- Jira
- Unity
- Unity Collab
- DevOps
- Microsoft Teams
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Flash
- Adobe XD
- Camtasia

## **Education**

Graduate Certificate Cyber Security and Networking (2021)

Melbourne Institute of Technology- Melbourne, VIC

# Bachelor of Games and Interactive Environments (Software Technologies) (2020)

Queensland University of Technology - Brisbane, QLD

Diploma of Digital Interactive Game Design (2017)

Queensland TAFE - Southbank, QLD

Senior Certificate (2016)

John Paul College - Daisy Hill, QLD

## Employment Referees:

**Scholastic** 

Achievements

OUT GPA:

Distinction

IPC Football

Tennis 2016

Second IX (TAS

Premiers 2016)

IPC Open B Boys'

Available upon request

## Employment-based Training

 Responsible Service of Alcohol (RSA) – Statement of Attainment 2017

## Volunteer Work

Over 2012-15, I assisted at the Anglican Church of Noosa in three roles:

- IT for Sunday Services
- Hospitality (morning teas)
  - Assistance to the Youth Group Supervisor

## **Employment**

June 2021 - current: Quality Assurance Engineer (full time)

Gameloft

Brisbane City QLD 4000

Responsibilities:

- · Querying cloud database using SQL Snowflake
- · Querying and graphing Snowflake queries into Looker API
- CI/CD pipeline Jenkins
- Reporting, reviewing and documenting bugs on Jira
- Working on The Oregon Trail Game
- iPhone, Mac OS, Apple tv use

# Feb 2021 - June 2021: Graduate Solutions Programmer / Support Engineer (Junior Developer) (full time)

Fileman

Paradise Point Qld 4216

Responsibilities:

- Programming, source control and code quality control
- Implementing new systems and features
- Bug fixing and code clean up
- Handling tickets from clients (legal professionals)
- Communicating with other team members and clients
- C# .NET/ASP.NET MVC
- ORM's
- JavaScript (jQuery & Bootstrap)
- Microsoft Office/365 SMTP & DKIM encryption
- SourceTree

## Sep 2018 - Sep 2021: Warehouse Picker/Packer/Loader (Casual)

Coles Distribution Centre

Forest Lake Qld 4077

Responsibilities:

- Order selection and packing for store distribution throughout whole of Queensland and northern NSW
- Quality control and loss prevention
- Dangerous goods awareness
- · Loading pallets to semi-trailers and operation of heavy machinery

## Jan 2018 - Sep 2018: IT Relocator (Casual)

Goals A+N

Geebung Qld 4034

## Responsibilities:

- Disassembling/reassembling IT systems
- QA (testing/functionality) of reassembled systems

Reason for Leaving: Focus on other casual roles with more consistent hours.

## Jan 2017 - Jan 2020: Event Staff - The Gabba (Casual)

Stadiums Queensland

Woolloongabba QLD 4102

## Responsibilities:

- Ushering and ticket collection for weekend sporting and major events
- Supervision of patron safety and behaviour
- Monitoring/servicing of premium seating and corporate seating areas

Reason for Leaving: Focus on studies and other casual positions.

### Feb 2017 - Sep 2018: Warehouse Picker/Packer - City Beach (Casual)

City Beach E-Store (Warehouse), Murrarie QLD 4172

Reason for Leaving: Successful application to Coles warehouse.

## Dec 2015 - Feb 2017: Mechanic's Assistant (Casual)

N & D Mechanical Repairs, Wacol QLD 4076

Reason for Leaving: Commenced university and other casual employment.